PAULINA WDOWICZ

ABOUT ME

Worked as a manual tester for a vehicle and human body simulation desktop program suite (engineering: traffic accident physical simulations). Experienced in cooperation with programming and QA teams to develop and ship bug-free, intuitive software. Participated in 2 program releases and 4minor patch releases. Previously, I worked in the field of waste management in the two largest waste management companies in Warsaw. My position required me to be precise, to pay attention to details, to stay in contact with customers and to meet deadlines. Passionate about video game.

CONTACT

- @ paulina.wdowicz1@gmail.com
- +48 534 068 439
- ⊠ Warsaw. Poland
- Github/PaulinaWdowicz
- LinkedIn/PaulinaWdowicz

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Lua
- Python

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Easy Redmine
- GIT
- SQL
- JIRA
- Mantis
- Microsoft Office

LANGUAGES

- Polish (mother language)
- English (B2)
- Russian (A1)

EXPERIENCE

2023.06-now **Junior Manual Tester** *CYBID Sp. z o.o sp. k.*

- Performing functional, regression and exploratory tests to detect defects and ensure compliance with software requirements.
- Documenting test results in Easy Redmine; reporting errors, issues and proposals for new UX/UI features; cooperation with developers.
- Designing, developing and maintaining LUA scripts that automate the testing process using the in-house software wrapper.
- Experienced in remote work (full-time).

2022.07–2023.06 Environmental protection and service specialist *EKO-BYŚ Sp. zo.o.*

- Preparing and submitting required waste reports and cooperation with institutions in the field of waste management (monthly/annual reports required by Polish law).
- Maintaining contacts and cooperation with clients (by phone, e-mail).

2019.01-2022.06 Waste management specialist

Miejskie Przedsiębiorstwo Oczyszczania w m. st. Warszawie Sp. z o.o.

- Maintaining documentation regarding waste generated by the facility and segregated secondary raw materials.
- Cooperation with external companies in the field of waste management.

2013.10-2019.09 Member

The Warsaw University of Technology Students' Council

EDUCATION

2013-2019 Warsaw University of Technology

Faculty of Building Services, Hydro and Environmental Engineering Environmental Protection course
Bachelor and Master level

COURSES AND TRAININGS

- Fundamentals of Software Testing QATestLab
- Manual Software Testing Basics Udemy
- Jira Beginners Course Project Management Udemy
- Introduction to SQL: Data Management and Querying Khan Academy

II agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).